Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Publications
  - Bulletins on school architecture & hygiene for the U.S. Office of Education
Henderson, Carrie June 3, 1927 3
Sweets, Henry H. June 3, 1927 3
Woodward, R. June 3, 1927 3
Brahan, T.S. June 7, 1927 3
Tidwell, R.E. June 13, 1927 3
Cook, Elmer June 16, 1927 3
Mowery, H.W. June 16, 1927 3
Sanders, J.E. June 16, 1927 3
Schiesz, L.B. June 16, 1927 3
Wiggins, H.B. June 16, 1927 3
Ganey, J.S. June 28, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. June 28, 1928 3
Wiggins, H.B. June 28, 1927 3
Wiggins, H.B. June 28, 1927 3
Wiggins, H.B. July 1, 1927 3
D.C. Heath & Co. July 2, 1927 3
Tucker, E.B. July 8, 1927 3
Blalock, Flora July 13, 1927 3
Foresman, Mary E. July 13, 1927 3
Laird, P.E. July 13, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. July 20, 1927 3
Emerson, D.W. July 28, 1927 3
Hardin, Jesse July 28, 1927 3
Lowrey, Dr. July 29, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. July 29, 1927 3
Graham, James M. Aug. 2, 1927 3
Hardin, Jesse Aug. 2, 1927 3
Hardin, Jesse Aug. 2, 1927 3
Williams, Zelia Aug. 2, 1927 3
Emerson, D.W. Aug. 12, 1927 3
Challman, Samuel A. Aug. 16, 1927 3
Manning, Mr. Aug. 16, 1927 3
Hellenic Information Bureau Aug. 24, 1927 3
Smith, Professor Aug. 27, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. Aug. 30, 1927 3
Brainerd, Heloise Sept. 23, 1927 3
Cullens, Helen Sept. 23, 1927 3
O’Shea, M.V. Sept. 23, 1927 3
Shackelford, E.M. Sept. 23, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. Sept. 23, 1927 3
Blakely, H.B. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Dittmar, Mr. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Hull, Emmett J. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Menon, H.B. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Menon, H.B. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Palmon, R.P. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Shackelford, E.M. Oct. 7, 1927 3
Bruce, Will C. Oct. 10, 1927 3
Ledbetter Oct. 17, 1927 3
Hendrickson, John J. Oct. 27, 1927 3
Hirst, C.M. Oct. 27, 1927 3
Laird, P.E. Oct. 27, 1927 3
Nichols, G.R. Oct. 27, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. Oct. 27, 1927 3
Willingham, H.J. Oct. 27, 1927 3
Ivy, H.M. Oct. 28, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. Oct. 31, 1927 3
Ivy, H.M. Oct. 31, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. Oct. 31, 1927 3
Rawlins, H.A. Nov. 8, 1927 3
Maxey, F.S. Nov. 11, 1927 3
Blakeley, H.B. Nov. 14, 1927 3
Ivy, H.M. Nov. 14, 1927 3
Willingham, Henry J. Nov. 14, 1927 3
Wood, Frank H. Nov. 23, 1927 3
Smith, J.H. Nov. 26, 1927 3
Allen, C.H. Dec. 8, 1927 3
Blakeley, H.B. Dec. 8, 1927 3
Farrington Co. Dec. 8, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. Dec. 8, 1927 3
Nichols, Mrs. G.R. Dec. 13, 1927 3
Willingham, Henry J. Dec. 14, 1927 3
Board of Education Dec. 16, 1927 3
Ivy, H.M. Dec. 16, 1927 3
Simmons, George C. Dec. 16, 1927 3
Reiff, E.K. Dec. 30, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. Dec. 30, 1927 3
Adair, Cornelia S. Jan. 3, 1928 3
O’Harrow, Omar Jan. 23, 1928 3
Stigler, Oren Jan. 23, 1928 3
Rochelle, W.L. Feb. 3, 1928 3
Rochelle, W. L. Feb. 8, 1928 3
Abbott, T.C. Feb. 13, 1928 3
Heidelberg, H.B. Feb. 13, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. Feb. 28, 1928 3
Challman, Samuel H. March 28, 192 3
Rogers, J.F. March 28, 192 3
Hirst, C.M. April 2, 1928 3
Rochelle, W.R. April 9, 1928 3
Cherry, T.C. April 18, 1928 3
University of North Carolina April 23, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell April 27, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. April 28, 1928 4
O’Shea, M.V. May 3, 1928 3
Kalbach, L.A. May 12, 1928 3
Bachman, Frank P. May 15, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell May 18, 1928 3
Wood, Frank H. May 18, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. May 29, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell June 2, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell June 11, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell June 25, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. June 28, 1928 3
Challman, Samuel A. July 7, 1928 3
Cherry, T.C. July 18, 1928 3
Echols, W.G. July 20, 1928 3
Edwards, John H. July 23, 1928 3
Whaley, Nell July 27, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell July 28, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. July 28, 1928 3
Upton, R.G. Aug. 2, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell Aug., 9, 1928 3
National Motion Pictures Co. Aug. 17, 1928 3
Orchard, Lucille Aug. 17, 1928 3
Thomas, D.E. Aug. 17, 1928 3
Upton, R.G. 17/08/28 3
Wood, Frank H. Aug. 17, 1928 3
Overton, John Aug. 23, 1928 3
Bruce, William C. Aug. 24, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell Aug. 24, 1928 3
Wood, Frank H. Aug. 27, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell Aug. 29, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. Aug. 29, 1928 3
Kalbach, L.A. Sept. 7, 1928 3
O’Steen, Myrtle Sept. 7, 1928 3
Shaw, O.A. Sept. 7, 1928 3
McCracken, C.C. Sept. 17, 1928 3
Tidwell, R.E. Sept. 17, 1928 3
Whaley, Nell Sept. 17, 1928 3
Thomas, D.E. Sept. 18, 1928 3
Tidwell, R.E. Sept. 18, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell Sept. 25, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. Sept. 28, 1928 3
Horn, J.F. Oct. 5, 1928 3
Whaley, Nell Oct. 15, 1928 3
Rogers, J.H. Oct. 29, 1928 3
Wood, Thomas D. Oct. 29, 1928 3
Whaley, Nell Nov. 2, 1928 3
Pruett, Haskell Nov. 20, 1928 3
Rogers, J.F. Nov. 28, 1928 3
Heidelberg, H.B. Dec. 12, 1928 3
Walker, Dora D. Dec. 24, 1928 3
Rogers, J.H. Dec. 29, 1928 3
Miller, J.C. Dec. 31, 1928 3
Saunders, G.W. Jan. 5, 1929 3
Pruett, Haskell Jan. 8, 1929 3
Thomas, D.E. Jan. 8, 1929 3
Camp, Annie Jan. 10, 1929 3
Tingle, Ruby Jan. 10, 1929 3
Nessley, Carl T. Jan. 12, 1929 3
Horn, J. Fred Jan. 15, 1929 3
Border, Clara V. Jan. 16, 1929 3
Byrne, Thomas W. Jan. 16, 1929 3
Walker, Dora Dee Jan. 16, 1929 3
Haddon, S.T. Jan. 30, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. Jan. 30, 1929 3
Eckles, W.G. Feb. 1, 1929 3
Wood, Thomas D. Feb. 1, 1929 3
Challman, Samuel A. Feb. 7, 1929 3
Pruett, Hasekll Feb. 7, 1929 3
Tidwell, R.E. Feb. 15, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 16, 1929 3
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 22, 1929 3
Frazier, John M. Feb. 22, 1929 3
Harvard Univ. Fellowship Cmte. Feb. 26, 1929 3
Rogers, J.F. Feb. 28, 1929 3
Bass, E.E. March 27, 192 3
Rogers, J.H. March 29, 192 3
Wood, Frank H. April 5, 1929 3
Donovan, John J. April 6, 1929 3
Howell, William H. AprilS, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. April 11, 1929 3
Barton, Eva April 12, 1929 3
Challman, Samuel April 15, 1929 3
MA Dept. of Public Health April 19, 1929 3
KS State Dept. of Education April 19, 1929 3
Bruce, William C. April 25, 1929 3
Moehlman, A.B. April 26, 1929 3
Sellers, Minnie April 26, 1929 3
Claxton, P.P. April 29, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. April 29, 1929 3
Bruce, William C. April 30, 1929 3
Graham, James L. May 1, 1929 3
Graham, James L. May 1, 1929 3
Endsley, J.R. May 2, 1929 3
Smith, S.L. May 4, 1929 3
U.S. Supervising Architect May 7, 1929 3
Graham, James L. May 8, 1929 3
Buice, W.A. May 10, 1929 3
Triest, R.M. May 10, 1929 3
Farmer, Dr. May 13, 1929 3
Graham, James L. May 13, 1929 3
Graham, James L. May 15, 1929 3
Donovan, John J. May 20, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. May 29, 1929 3
Peterson, Kimbark June 7, 1929 3
Phelps, Shelton June 7, 1929 3
Lay, Isabel R. June 14, 1929 3
Stankard, Katherine E. June 14, 1929 3
Crabb, A.L. June 28, 1929 3
Rogers, J.F. June 28, 1929 3
Rogers, J.F. June 28, 1929 3
Shumate, Mamie June 28, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. June 29, 1929 3
Rose, Thelma July 5, 1929 3
Schuyler, Paul M. July 9, 1929 3
Moehlman, A.B. July 10, 1929 3
Roemer, Joseph July 11, 1929 3
Moehlman, A.B. July 15, 1929 3
Moehlman, Dr. & Mrs. A.B. July 26, 1929 3
Payne, Bruce R. July 27, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. July 31, 1929 3
Schmidt, H.W. JUly 31, 1929 3
Hollis, L.P. Aug. 9, 1929 3
Hirst, C.M. Aug. 20, 1929 3
Graham, W.F. Sept. 16, 1929 3
Krill, J.J. Sept. 16, 1929 3
Geiger, W.T.P. Sept. 17, 1929 3
Branch, Fannie Sept. 19, 1929 3
Caswell, Ellie Sept. 20, 1929 3
Gregory, Mrs. Irwin 0. Sept. 20, 1929 3
Challman, Samuel H. Sept. 23, 1929 3
Green, Eloise Sept. 23, 1929 3
Hutchinson, Iva Sept. 23, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Sept. 23, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. Sept. 28, 1929 3
Goodykoontz, Bess Oct. 10, 1929 3
Rogers, J.F. Oct. 10, 1929 3
Betel, James 0. Oct. 28, 1929 3
Carpenter, W.W. Oct. 28, 1929 3
Krill, J.J. Oct. 28, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. Oct. 30, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 2, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 6, 1929 3
Towner, Isabel L. Nov. 11, 1929 3
Evans, Henry R. Nov. 13, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 15, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 19, 1929 3
McCornack, W.R. Nov. 19, 1929 3
Schmidt, H.W. Nov. 19, 1929 3
Blair, John J. Nov. 21, 1929 3
Pruett, Haskell Nov. 21, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 22, 1929 3
Russon, L.P. Nov. 22, 1929 3
Evans, Henry R. Nov. 24, 1929 3
McCornack, Walter R. Nov. 24, 1929 3
Wynn, William T. Nov. 26, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. Nov. 29, 1929 3
Bristol, L.R. Nov. 30, 1929 3
Rice, Elwood E. Dec. 1, 1929 3
Upson, Arthur T. Dec. 1, 1929 3
Doster, James J. Dec. 2, 1929 3
Scherer, Francis R. Dec. 2, 1929 3
Dennis, John C. Dec. 3, 1929 3
Finegan, Thomas E. Dec. 4, 1929 3
Rogers, J.H. Dec. 6, 1929 3
Kalbach, L.A. Dec. 9, 1929 3
Prall, C.E. Dec. 10, 1929 3
Bristol, L.R. Dec. 11, 1929 3
Prall, C.A. Dec. 27, 1929 3
Evans, Henry R. Dec. 30, 1929 3
Rogers, J.F. Dec. 30, 1929 3
Coope, W.J. Dec. 31, 1929 3
Bachman, Dr. undated 3
Betelle, James 0. undated 3
Boykin, J.C. undated 3
Braden, W.H. undated 3
Burroughs, Nannie H. undated 3
Burton, A. C. undated 3
Clark, Walter E. undated 3
Claxton, P.P. undated 3
Commissioner of Education undated 3
Considine, Miss undted 3
Coolidge, C.E. undated 3
Cooper, Frank Irving undated 3
Cubberly, Ellwood P. undated 3
Delima, A. undated 3
Eitel, H.C. undated 3
Holland, E.O. undated 3
Jones, E.W. undated 3
Kalbach, L.A. undated 3
Kingsley, Sherman C. undated 3
LeGarde, Ellen undated 3
McClure, John M. undated 3
Maphis, Charles G. undated 3
Mulligan, Mr. undated 3
Payne, Dr. undated 3
Peterson, E.A. undated 3
Pratt, Mr. undated 3
Rogers, J.F. undated 3
Ryan, W. Carson undated 3
Sibley, Mr. undated 3
State of ALabama undated 3
Tigert, J.J. undated 3
Urquhart, James B. undated 3
Watkins & Watkins undated 3
Wilbur, G. Elmer undated 3
Wood, Thomas D. undated 3
Wright, Mr. undated 3
Unidentified undated 3